Hi, I'm Julian from Taylor Intelligence
and now the third thing that we offer is
education. So just because we deliver AI
to your team does not mean everyone's
going to know how to use it. So most
employees now may avoid AI, kind of know
how to use it, or experiment
inefficiently. Let's get past that and
have us educate your team. We work through
real scenarios with customers to make sure
you're actually learning the spots where
AI can help. It's not just a generic
presentation and our goal is not to have
your whole team be AI experts but to have
everyone have a certain fluency in AI that
they can tell when to use it, how to be
responsible with its use, and even when
human judgment is necessary. If you want
to have your team learn about AI today
then train them below.